Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files /4178
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files
1989- 1991
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
Martin P. Catherwood Library
Miller, J. Gormly
Harper, Shirley
/4178
4 cubic feet
4 linear ft.
Records (documents), case files.
3108969
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 27, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 03, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4004: ILR School Librarian's Office Files /4108: ILR School Librarian's Office Additional Files /4139: Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files /4145: ILR School Librarian's Office Additional Files /4156: ILR School Librarian's Office Additional Files /4169: Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files /4172: Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files /4178: Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files
Harper, Shirley F.; Miller, J. Gormly; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; Martin P. Catherwood Library.; Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office.
3108969
- Requisitions: "A" General (1989-91) (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Requisitions: Administrative Management Society (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Requisitions: Advanced Image Management (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Requisitions: AFC-CIO (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Requisitions: African Imprint Library Services (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Requisitions: Akateeminen Kinkjakauppa (1991) (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Requisitions: Almovist and Wiskell International (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Requisitions: American, General (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Requisitions: American Arbitration Association (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Requisition: ARL Office Management Studies (1991) (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Requisition: Association of Negotiators and Contract Administrations (1989-91) (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Requisitions: Audio/Video Distributors (1989-91) (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Requisitions: Audio Visual Systems, Inc. (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Requisitions: Aux. Amateurs De Livies International (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Requisitions: Australia General (1987-91) (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Requisitions: "B" General (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Requisitions: Ballen (1989-90) (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Requisitions: Bender, Matthew (1989-91) (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Requisitions: Bennett, James (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Requisitions: Besnan (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Requisitions: Bibliography Retrieval Services (1989-91) (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Requisitions: Blackwell (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Old Requisitions: Boleium (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Old Requisitions: Books from Mexico (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Old Requisitions: Botes Library (1989-91) (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Old Requisitions: RR Bowker (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Old Requisitions: Brodart (1990) (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Old Requisitions: Bunaff Publications (1989-91) (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Old Requisition: The Bureau of National Affairs (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Old Requisitions: BNA Books (1989-91) (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Old Requisitions: Business and Legal Reports (1989-91) (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Old Requisitions: Butterworks (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Old Requisitions: "C" General (1987-91) (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Old Requisitions: California, State of (1989-91) (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Old Requisitions: California, University of (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Old Requisitions: Callaghan and Co. (1989-91) (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Old Requisitions: Canada, General (1989-91) (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Old Requisitions: Canada Law Book, Inc. (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Old Requisitions: Canadian Government Publishing Center (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Old Requisitions: Caribbean Imprint Library Services (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Old Requisitions: Carswell Legal Publications (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Old Requisitions: Casalini Library (1989-91) (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Old Requisitions: Center on Budget and Policy Priorities (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Old Requisitions: Central New York Copiers (1985-91) (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Old Requisitions: Clark, Boardman, Callahan (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Old Requisitions: Columbia, University of (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Old Requisitions: Commerce Clearing House (1987-91) (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Old Requisitions: Compuserve, Inc. (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Old Requisitions: Computing Center (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Old Requisitions: The Conference Board (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Old Requisitions: Congressional Info. Services (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Old Requisitions: Congressional Quarterly, Inc. (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Old Requisitions: Conservation Info. Network (1991) (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Old Requisitions: Copy Machine Supply (1989-91) (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Old Requisitions: Cornell Daily Sun (1989-91) (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Old Requisitions: Cornell University (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Old Requisitions: CU Administrative Operations (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Old Requisitions: CU Insurance (1991) (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Old Requisitions: CU Dialogue Info. Services (1991) (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Old Requisitions: CU Messenger Expense (1990-91) (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Old Requisitions: CU (1991) (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Old Requisitions: CU Maintenance and Service Operations (1990-91) (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Old Requisitions: CU State College Fleet (1988-91) (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Old Requisitions: CU Stores Enterprises (1991) (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Old Requisitions: Coutt Library Service (1990-91) (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Old Requisitions: Crown Publications (1990-91) (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Old Requisitions: "D" General (1989-91) (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Old Requisitions: Data, General (1990-91) (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Old Requisitions: Demco (1990-91) (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Old Requisitions: Documents Index Guide to US Government Statistics and Periodicals (1990-91) (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Old Requisitions: Dow Jones Info Service (1989-91) (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Old Requisitions: "E" General (1990-91) (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Old Requisitions: Ebsco (1991) (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Old Requisitions: Ebsco (1989) (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Old Requisitions: Ebsco Online (1987-91) (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Old Requisitions: Sibley Real Estate Services (1990-91) (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Old Requisitions: Executive Telecom (1990-91) (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Old Requisitions: "F" General (1990-91) (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Old Requisitions: Federal Express (1989-91) (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Old Requisitions: Ann Filando (1990-91) (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Old Requisitions: "G" General (1989-91) (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Old Requisitions: Gale Research Company (1990-91) (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Old Requisitions: Gaylord Brothers (1990-91) (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Old Requisitions: Greenwood Press (1990-91) (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Old Requisitions: Gnomon (1990-91) (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Old Requisitions: "H" General (1990-91) (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Old Requisitions: Hamilton, Alexander Corp. (1989-91) (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Old Requisitions: Harassowitz, Otto (1990-91) (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Old Requisitions: Harrison Company (1990-91) (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Old Requisitions: Hawaii, University of (1990-91) (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Old Requisitions: Hewitt Associates (1990-91) (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Old Requisitions: Highsmith (1990-91) (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Old Requisitions: Hollinger Corporation (1990-91) (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Old Requisitions: HR Systems Professionals (1990) (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Old Requisitions: "I" General (1990-91) (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Old Requisitions: Incomes Data Services, Ltd., England (1990-91) (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Old Requisitions: Industrial Relations Research Association (1989-91) (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Old Requisitions: Information on Demand (1991) (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Old Requisitions: Input Culture Company (1991) (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Old Requisitions: Input Culture Company (1990) (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Old Requisitions: Interdepartmental Orders (1990-91) (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Old Requisitions: Insights (1990-91) (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Old Requisitions: Interdepartmental Orders (1991) (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Old Requisitions: Interdepartmental Orders - Debits (1990) (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Old Requisitions: International Foundation of Employee Benefit Plans - Membership (1990-91) (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Old Requisitions: International Industrial Relations Association (1990-91) (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Old Requisitions: International Labor Office (1990-91) (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Old Requisitions: International Personnel Management Association (1990-91) (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Old Requisitions: International Social Security Association (1990-91) (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Old Requisitions: "J" General (1990-91) (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Old Requisitions: Jai Press, Inc. (1989-91) (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Old Requisitions: Japan Publications Trading Co., Ltd. (1990-91) (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Old Requisitions: Journal Entries (1991) (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Old Requisitions: Journal Entries (1990) (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Old Requisitions: "K" General (1989-91) (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Old Requisitions: "L" General (1989-91) (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Old Requisitions: Labor Relations Press (1989-91) (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Old Requisitions: Labor Research Association (1989-91) (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Old Requisitions: The Lawyers Co-Op Publishing Company (1990-91) (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Old Requisitions: Lenz and Riecker (1989-91) (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Old Requisitions: Library of Congress (1990-91) (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Old Requisitions: "M" General (1990-91) (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Old Requisitions: Maine Department of Labor (1990-91) (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Old Requisitions: Michigan Library Consortium (1990-91) (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Old Requisitions: Michigan, University of (1990-91) (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Old Requisitions: Mead Data Corporation (1989-91) (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Old Requisitions: 3M Company (1990-91) (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Old Requisitions: Misco (1990-91) (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Old Requisitions: MIT Sloan School (1990-91) (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Old Requisitions: "N" General (1991) (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Old Requisitions: "N" General (1990) (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Old Requisitions: Naco Electronics (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Old Requisitions: National Audio/Visual Supply (1989-91) (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Old Requisitions: National Bureau of Economic Research (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Old Requisitions: National Center for Employee Ownership (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Old Requisitions: National Committee on Pay Equity (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Old Requisitions: National Register Publishing Company (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Old Requisition: National Safe Workplace Institute (1989-91) (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Old Requisitions: The National Underwriter Company (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Old Requisitions: New England Legal Publisher (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Old Requisitions: Newsnet Online Services (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Old Requisitions: Newspaper Delivery Service, Ithaca (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Old Requisitions: New York, General (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Old Requisitions: New Zealand, General (1989-91) (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Old Requisitions: Nihoff International (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Old Requisitions: "O" General (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Old Requisitions: OECD (1989-91) (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Old Requisitions: Ofihian Press (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Old Requisitions: "P" General (1989-91) (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Old Requisitions: The Paige Company (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Old Requisitions: Passim (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Old Requisitions: Panel Publishing Inc. (1990) (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Old Requisitions: PBS Video (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Old Requisitions: PC Connection (1989-91) (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Old Requisitions: Personal Bibliographic Software (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Old Requisitions: Personnel Management Abstracts (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Old Requisitions: Prentice Hall (1990) (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Old Requisitions: Public Affairs Information Service, Inc. (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Old Requisitions: "Q" General (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Old Requisitions: "R" General (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Old Requisitions: Rockefeller Institute (1990) (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Old Requisitions: "S" General (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Old Requisitions: Sage Publications, Inc. (1990) (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Old Requisitions: Sentry Business Products (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Old Requisitions: Shepard's Citations (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Old Requisitions: South Central Research Library Council (1991) (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Old Requisitions: Special Libraries Association (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Old Requisitions: State Historical Society of Wisconsin (1989-90) (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Old Requisitions: Statistics Canada (1989) (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Old Requisitions: "T" General (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Old Requisitions: TNT Red Star Express (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Old Requisitions: Tompkins-Seneca-Tioga BOCES (1991) (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Old Requisitions: Triangle Book Shop (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Old Requisitions: "U" General (1989-91) (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Old Requisitions: UNIPUB (1989-91) (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Old Requisitions: United Nations (1989-91) (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Old Requisitions: United States, General (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Old Requisitions: US Government Printing Office Account #0732636 (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Old Requisitions: University, General (1989-91) (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Old Requisitions: University Microfilms (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Old Requisitions: Urban Institute (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Old Requisitions: "V" General (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Old Requisitions: Vance (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Old Requisitions: Vu/Text (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Old Requisitions: "W" General (1989-91) (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Old Requisitions: Warren, Gorham and Lamont (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 57)
- Old Requisitions: Washington Researchers Ltd. (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 58)
- Old Requisitions: West Publishing (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 59)
- Old Requisitions: Wiley, John and Sons (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 60)
- Old Requisitions: Wilson, H.W. Company (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 61)
- Old Requisitions: Word Perfect Corporation (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 62)
- Old Requisitions: "XYZ" General (1990-91) (Box 4, Folder 63)
- Old Requisitions: Xerox Corporation (1989-91) (Box 4, Folder 64)
- Old Requisitions: Yankee Book Peddler (1991) (Box 4, Folder 65)